The biggest underdog story ever.
Rumble is a animation, family film directed by Hamish Grieve.
In a world where monster wrestling is a global sport and monsters are superstar athletes, teenage Winnie seeks
to follow in her father’s footsteps by coaching a loveable underdog monster into a champion.
Steve (voice), played by Will Arnett.
Winnie (voice), played by Geraldine Viswanathan.
Marc Remy (voice), played by Stephen A. Smith.
Tentacular (voice), played by Terry Crews.
Lights Out McGinty (voice), played by Jimmy Tatro.
Ramarilla (voice), played by Joe Anoa'i.
Rumble is a 2021 American animated sports comedy film directed by
Hamish Grieve and written by Grieve and Matt Lieberman.
Loosely based on Monster on the Hill, a graphic novel by Rob Harrell, the film stars
the voices of Will Arnett, Geraldine Viswanathan, and Terry Crews.
Set in a world where humans and giant monsters exist, an aspiring trainer trains an
amateur giant monster wrestler to go up against the world champion.
The film was released in the United States on December 15, 2021, on
Paramount+, and received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of monster, wrestling, based on comic, kaiju, amused.